itt-tech.edu 2016-09-06

# ITT Technical Institute | Privacy Policy

##  ITT TECHNICAL INSTITUTE

* * *

The ITT Technical Institutes understand that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to its web site (the "Site") and recognizes their obligations to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why the ITT Technical Institutes maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you.

## Sites Covered by this Policy

Each ITT Technical Institute is part of a nationwide organization, with legal entities, business processes, management structures and technical systems that cross state borders. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to all websites and domain owned by the ITT Technical Institutes, except that a privacy statement posted on an ITT Tech website specific to a particular ITT Tech program will apply instead of this Policy.

## Collection of Information

You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, address, phone number, email address or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to have access to some features of the Site. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain offerings, services or products. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP address (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means. We hope that, by using Anonymous Information, we can update the site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation.

## Use of Information

ITT Tech uses your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your requests; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to notify you of our offerings, services and products that may be of interest to you; to provide Internet security; and to meet legal requirements. ITT Tech may work with associated businesses which may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing services to users. These businesses have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. We may use third party advertising companies to place ads on the Site and to place our ads on other web sites. If ITT Tech is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information may be among the transferred assets.

## Privacy of Children

ITT Tech encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law.

## Your Opportunity to Opt-out of Email Advertising

In the event you do not wish to receive promotional email from ITT Tech, follow the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive.

## Cookies

When you visit the Site, ITT Tech or a third party may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions. If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Site's features.

## Links

The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. If you access those links, you will leave the ITT Tech website. ITT Tech does not control those third-party sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from ITT Tech's privacy practices. ITT Tech does not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The personal data you choose to provide to or that is collected by those third parties is not covered by the ITT Tech Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any website before submitting your personal information.

ITT Tech may also provide social media features on the Site that enable you to share information with your social networks and to interact with us on various social media sites. Your use of these features may result in the collection or sharing of information about you, depending on the feature. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and settings on the social media sites with which you interact to make sure you understand the information that could be shared by those sites.

## Security

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on our secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution.

## Phishing Scams

It is a policy of ITT Tech to not send unsolicited emails seeking certain highly sensitive personal information, such as social security number, date of birth or credit card number. In the event you receive such an email, and you have not previously been in direct contact with its sender, please do not respond and do not open any attachments as they may contain malicious code that will infect your computer.

## Changes to the Policy

We may modify this Policy at any time by posting a revised version of the Policy here, with an updated effective date. Accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent. By using the Site and providing us with your personally identifiable information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy.

## California Do Not Track Disclosure

Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to websites with which the browser communicates. ITT Tech does not currently respond to these signals. Third parties, including our service providers, may collect information about your online activities over time and across different Web sites, including when you visit our Web site. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about how to exercise choice regarding the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services. To learn more about these advertising practices or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

## Deletion Rights of Minors

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. Currently, ITT Tech does not publicly post any such content. 

## Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code permits customers of a business who are California residents to request that the business not share their personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Currently, ITT Tech does not share its customers' personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Please see the Sections entitled "Collection of Information", "Use of Information", "Your Opportunity to Opt-out of Email Advertising", and "Cookies" for additional information.

Effective 2015
